{
    "subject": "resource/Sigrid_Undset",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Nobel_laureates_in_Literature",
    "human_readable": "Sigrid Undset is a Nobel laureate in Literature.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8696079850196838,
            "question": "What field did Sigrid Undset win a Nobel Prize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8263542056083679,
            "question": "Was Sigrid Undset a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8085232377052307,
            "question": "When did Sigrid Undset win the Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7898176908493042,
            "question": "Who is Sigrid Undset?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.74901282787323,
            "question": "What impact did Sigrid Undset have on literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6858454346656799,
            "question": "What is Sigrid Undset known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6096635460853577,
            "question": "What other notable achievements did Sigrid Undset have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.560240626335144,
            "question": "Where was Sigrid Undset from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5177966356277466,
            "question": "Why is Sigrid Undset considered a significant figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4458426535129547,
            "question": "What are some of Sigrid Undset's most famous works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sigrid Undset is a Nobel laureate in Literature.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2615_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is Sigrid Undset considered a significant figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2615_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Sigrid Undset from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2615_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other notable achievements did Sigrid Undset have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2615_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2615_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references that Sigrid Undset was indeed a Nobel laureate in Literature, including details about her winning the prize in 1928 for her descriptions of life during the Middle Ages in Scandinavia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}